(Howard:)Hey, Raj, what's up?
(Raj:)You were right. I can't get out of here.
- You're still at my mother's?
- I'm trapped.
(Raj:)My clothes have been in the laundry
all day, and she hid my keys.
(Raj:)I think they might be in her bra
because she jingles when she walks.
(Raj:)What do I do?
(Howard:)Hey, you wanted a woman in your life,
now you got one.
(Raj:)Come on, Howard, help me.
Rajesh, tatellah, I ran you a bath!
(Raj:)Oh, my God,
she's not gonna bathe me, is she?
(Howard:)Gee, I wish I could tell you no.
(Howard:)All right, well, thanks again
for helping me out.
(Scene:)Howard...
- Should we go back and rescue him?
- Too late. We'll see him at his bar mitzvah.
(Sheldon:)Here you go.
(Amy:)I picked up the Chinese food
just the way Leonard used to.